<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://showerloop.cc/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://showerloop.cc/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Ways to Be Economical When Showering With an Injury</title>
      <link>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog4/</guid>
      <description>It’s extremely challenging to lead your daily life while sustaining an injury. And yet, dealing with sports injuries is something that most of us will have to go through, with nearly 2 million sports-related injuries affecting high school athletes alone per year. Most of us know the feeling of attempting to take a shower or bath when your arm is wrapped in a cast and cannot get wet. It’s a defeated feeling, and it can quickly take away the motivation to shower or bathe in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Put These Things Down The Shower Drain!</title>
      <link>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog3/</guid>
      <description>Natural water in Finland is some of the most polluted water in Europe (read the discussions in the article). You might be contributing to its pollution without realizing it, such as if you’re putting things down the drain that you really shouldn’t. Making your shower eco-friendly should be about saving water as well as preventing water contamination. Here’s what you can do to be greener and cleaner!
In Finland, people use an average of 140 liters of water every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showerloop at the Design museum</title>
      <link>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog2/</guid>
      <description>Low poly showerstall for the Design Museum. Enter &amp;amp; Encounter Exhibit At the start of the year, we were asked to bring a demo of Showerloop to an art/design/futurism exhibit. We also designed a wooden shower stall to accompany the showerloop system. The shower stall was made with blender, Explision, Meshlab, a lasercutter, circle saw, router, dremel, drill, clamps, hammer, crowbar, screwdriver, nuts, sticks, planks and bits, interior wax and lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The electronics board PCBBasic2.0</title>
      <link>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://showerloop.cc/posts/blog1/</guid>
      <description>For the last couple of months we have gotten back to circuit boards and looking at completing the project we started a long time ago. Making the shower smart and easily controllable like one would expect from modern consumer products. There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot to learn considering all we could do a few years ago was wire up a light bulb, and even then we would need to check what the difference was with the brown wire (live/positive) and the blue wire (ground/neutral).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>